apmoller.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy

**1\. General information**  
A.P. Møller - Mærsk A/S and the A.P. Moller – Maersk group (the "A.P. Moller – Maersk Group") recognizes and respects the privacy of our customers. Your privacy is important to the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group and therefore the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group is committed to respecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal data. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") gives an account of which personal data are collected when you access our website ("Web Site") and use our any of services ("Services") and of how such personal data are processed by the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group. By visiting the Web Site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group’s Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Web Site.

**2\. Collection of personal data**  
You will be informed prior to any collection of personal data when you use the Web Site or Services. We do not collect personal data about visitors to this Web Site unless provided voluntarily. The personal data collected via the Web Site may include your name and email address and similar contact information as well as other data relevant for the use of our Services. We will not use your personal data for marketing purposes without your express prior consent hereto.  
This site is a general audience site, and the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group does not knowingly collect personal data from any person under the age of 18 without parental consent.

**3\. Use of your personal data  
** We collect your personal data for the purpose of providing you with our Services and to accommodate your requests or inquiries. E.g. if you send email inquiries to the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group, your personal information, including your email address, will be used only for the purpose of responding to your inquiry. Furthermore, we collect your personal data in order to conduct statistical analysis pertaining to the use of the Web Site. These statistics are used to better serve our customers.  
The A.P. Moller – Maersk Group is a global company and personal data collected by the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group through this Web Site may be transferred among our various divisions and affiliated companies around the world located inside or outside the European Economic Area (EEA), as well to data processors outside of the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group. By submitting data on this Web Site, you consent to such transfer. Other than to data processors as indicated above the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group will not transfer your personal data to any third party outside the A.P. Moller – Maersk Group without the collection of your express prior consent hereto unless obligated to do so under applicable law.

**4\. Cookies  
** The A.P. Moller – Maersk Group may use information storage (commonly known as cookies) to allow you to use our site more easily and to allow us to keep track of certain statistical information that helps us improve our site. Our cookies do not contain personally identifiable data. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you wish, you may instruct your internet browser to prevent cookies from being used and to delete existing cookies. However, please note that the high quality of our Web Site may be reduced as a consequence hereof. Please refer to the help guide for your browser for further guidance. 

**5\. Security  
** The A.P. Moller – Maersk Group takes all appropriate organisational and technical security measures to protect your personal data and has thus, implemented necessary security measures in order to safeguard your data.

**6\. Access to your personal data etc.  
** You have the right to gain access to the data processed about you, however, with certain legal limitations. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data and to rectify the data processed if relevant.  
If you wish to exercise your right of access to your personal data, to object to the processing or to rectify processed data please contact Group Relations at [press@maersk.com](mailto:press@maersk.com) .

**7\. Modifications to the Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact Group Relations at [press@maersk.com](mailto:press@maersk.com) .
